Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Series II. Organizations
  - POR-WOM
    - Women Make Movies, Inc. - FY2003, EMF, 1993, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
      development report, press packet for Forbidden Love
    - Women's International Film, Inc. - Radio Bandung-2nd Decade Films - FY1997, EMF, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Grant application materials, background information, course and event materials
    - Binder of Digital Media Organizations and Conferences, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Volume 1)
      Turbulence; Floating Points: Net Art Now at Emerson College; Blast Theory; Downtown Digital Features; Digital Salon; Eye Wash; CEPA Gallery; P.O.V.; Teen to Teen Television; Third World Newsreel; African American Women in Cinema; D.U.M.B.O. Short Film and Video Festival; New American Radio
- Individuals A-Z
  - A-C
    - Aaron, Jane - Video Repertoire, Ltd. (FA 2), c. 1985, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1987-1988) for Set in Motion: Traveling Light
    - Abarca, Luis - Camera News (VD 1)(IND), c. 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      Grant application (FY92, FY94) for Danny and Chicha; copies of news clippings; letter of agreement
    - Abbott, Abdul - Boys Choir of Harlem (VD 1), c. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for video of the choir; letter of agreement
    - Abrams, Muhal Richard - Association for the Advancement of Creativity (JZ 1), 1987-1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      Grant applications for music compositions; letters of agreement; biographical information on Muhal Richard Abrams
    - Abuda, Ernest - Pan Asian Repertory, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      Grant application (1989-1990) for Cambodia Agonistes
    - Acconci, Vito - Haleakala (VA 30 E1), c. 1984 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Discipline
    - Acero, Raul - Empire State Crafts Alliance (SC 1), 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Votives for the Natural World a sculptural installation
    - Adams, Denis - Haleakala, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Bus Shelter Exhibition program; correspondence; letter of agreement; list of Visual Artists - Sponsored Projects and conflicts
    - Adolphe, Bruce - Turtle Bay/Meridian String Quartet (CH 1), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      Letter of agreement; biography of Bruce Adolphe
    - Ahwesh, Peggy - Women Make Movies (VE 1), c. 1992, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      Grant application (1992-1993, FY96) for Between Sisters and Lies and Excess
    - Aitken, Doug, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Correspondence; project description for Eraser; resume; press materials
    - Aikin, Susana - Post Vanguard (VD 4), 1989-1990, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for The Salt Mines; correspondence
    - Ainouz, Karim - New York Lesbian and Gay Experimental Film Festival (VE 2) (IND), c. 1994 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Grant application FY94 for Seams
    - Alam, Juan - African Caribbean Poetry (89-1106), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      CV for Juan Alan; correspondence
    - Allison, Jay - Audio Documentary Narrative, Radio Foundation (AN 17), c. 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Animal Radio
    - Allport, Catherine G. (Ph 2), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Correspondence; grant application 1987-1988 for Apartheid No!; press release for a Catskill Center for Photography grant; letter of agreement
    - Allyn, J. - Interaction Dance (PE 4), 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Angels Have Been Sent to ME; slides; copies of news clippings; correspondence
    - Alston, Macky - Media Network (VD 5), 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Grant application for Family Name; news clippings; CV for Macky Alston; correspondence; press packet; letter of agreement
    - Alvarez, Lynne - Women's Project, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for a commissioned play; letter of agreement; part of a CV for Lynne Alverez
    - Alvarez, Louis and Kolker (VD 7), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for For Beautiful Human Life
    - Amacher, Maryanne - Harvestworks (AI 9)(IND), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Grant application FY95 for The Levi-Montalcini Variations
    - Anderson, Kelly - American Social History Production (VD 6) (IND), c. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Letter of agreement, treatment for Out at Work
    - Andres, Jo - Women Make Movies, Inc. (VE 5), c. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Grant application FY98 for Visions in the House of Baba Yaga
    - Aparico, Carolos - Post Vanduard (VD 4), 1991-1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      CV and background information on Carlos Aparicio; grant application 1991-1992 for Save My Child; correspondence; schedule for Streetlife film festival; Downtown Community Television Center grant materials
    - Araujo, Jose - New York Fund for the Arts (N003), c. 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      press packets; background information on Jose Araujo; letter of agreement (1999); payment and reporting schedule
    - Archer, Julie - Mabou Mines (De 02), c. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      press packet; grant application 1994-1995 for The Epidog
    - Argento, Dominick (V22), c. 1989-1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Correspondence, grant application (undated) for music composition
    - Arlyck, Ralph - Upstate Films (VD 7), 1987, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Grant application (1989-990, FY98) for Current Events and untitled film about the 1960s; correspondence; letter of agreement (1989); copies of news clippings
    - Armstrong, Renee - Hallwalls, Inc. (WS001), 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for stage production; packet of supporting materials; correspondence; letter of agreement
    - Arnone, John - Downtown Art, c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for A Cool Million; copies of news clippings; description of Downtown Art Company; slides
    - Ashhurst, Carmen (VD 7), c. 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for film on John Coltrane
    - Ash-MacKay, Noreen - NYFA (VD 12), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Grant application 1990 Housebreak
    - Atlas, Charles - Haleakala, Inc. (VA 8), c. 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Program for S and D; copies of news clippings (1986)
    - Atkins, Shawn - Women Make Movies, Inc. (VA 5), c. 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Grant application FY97 for Frame by Frame Fierce; CVs for Shawn Atkins, Luna Lewis Ortiz, Fernanda Rossi Smelaski; status report
    - Avalos, Tony - Camera News (VD 7), 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Correspondence; grant application 1991-1992 for Reflections on the American Dream
    - Aylon, Helene - NYFA (VI 85), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Grant application FY95 for two sacs for 95; programs about the piece on the 50th anniversary of the bombing of Hiroshima and Nagasaki; correspondence; news clippings; in progress report
    - B, Beth - WS002 (IND), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for Room 214
    - B, Beth, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      NYSCA Letter of agreement rider; panel comments; press materials for Battlefields of Recovery; director, crew and consultant resumes; film information (synopsis, goals, audience and distribution, etc.)
    - B, Beth (VD 6), 1991-1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Grant application materials (1991-1992; 1992-1993; 1995; 1997) for Double Tracking, untitled film anthology, Inside Out and Whacked; copies of news clippings; press release; fliers
    - Babcock, Jo Ph183 (IND), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Lens on Wheels
    - Bach Laurence and Goolrick, Robert, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Visual Studies Workshop agreement for The Paros Dream Book; photographs by Laurence Bach and Robert Goolrick
    - Bacher, Fred - CTR Exploratory and Percep Art, (PH 86) (VA 8), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Can We Talk
    - Baer, Suzie, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Letter of agreement; panel comments; CV for Suzie Baer
    - Balcells, Eugenia/ Van Ripper (VI 6), c. 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Seeing the Dance; progress report
    - Ball, Janice (AD 7), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Against All Odds: Two Stories of Survival; correspondence
    - Barber, Stephen - Concert Artists Guild, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Sample of work submitted form; letter of agreement; biography of Stephen Barber
    - Barr, Burt (IN 10), c. 1987-1991, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Correspondence; grant application (1986-1987; 1989-1990; FY97) for untitled video piece, The Pool, and River Vista; progress report
    - Barrios, Jaime (VD 9), c. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for The New Crusaders
    - Barrios, Jamie - Alternative Media Information Center, Inc. (VD 8), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Neruda
    - Barry, Judith - Artists Space (VA 15), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for (Vampry); correspondence; Museum of Modern Art brochure Projects: Judith Barry
    - Battaglia, Skip - Pyramid Arts Center (VA 15), c. 1988, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      Grant application (1989-1990, FY98) for Restlessness and Second Nature
    - Bautis, Marta N. - Women Make Movies, Inc. (VD 13), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      Correspondence; grant application FY97 for Morir por Amor: Latinas and AIDS
    - Beatty, Maria (VD 13), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      Letter of agreement, grant application (undated) for Sphinxes Without Secrets: Women Performance Artists Speak Out
    - Beaumont, Betty - Women’s Studio Workshop (GR 17), c. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Fish Tales
    - Becker, Edith M. - Women's International Film (VD 15), c. 1992 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      Grant application FY92 for When the Spill Hit Homer; letter of agreement; grant report
    - Beckman, Erika (VE 17), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for The Beanstalk and Jack; a book for the film
    - Beebe, Dick - En Garde Arts, c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Farewell to Flesh
    - Beens, Olivia (PE 7), c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Beware of the Moving Platform
    - Uehara, Kazuo - Music from Japan (EL 139), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      Grant application FY90 for music composition; news clippings; programs (in English and Japanese). Note: Found out of alphabetical order but it relates to the next alpha entry
    - Behrman, David - Music from Japan (EL 119), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      Correspondence; grant application FY90 for music composition; copies of news clippings
    - Behrman, Davis - Elaine Summers E.I.F. (AA 17), c. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for interactive computer music installation
    - Bejar, Alfredo - Latino Collaborative (VN 18), c. 1990, 1995, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      Grant application (FY90 and FY96) for Women's Work and Getting to Heaven; script for Ganarse El Cielo; correspondence; letter of agreement (1995)
    - Bell, Matrin - NYFA (VD 15) (IND), c. 1994, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      Grant application FY94 for film about American children of parents with AIDS; made with Mary Ellen Mark
    - Beloff, Zoe - Harvestworks (NT237), c. 1997 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      Grant application FY97 for Beyond (World Wide Web Project) - interactive work on CD ROM; correspondence
    - Belsey, Laura -Wooster Group (VA 21) (IND), 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Three Sisters, letter of agreement, correspondence
    - Bender, Gretchen - CTR Exploratory and Perceptual Art (P 7), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      Correspondence; grant application 1986-1987 for Total Recall; copies of news clippings; fliers
    - Benoit, Patricia - National Coalition for Haitian Rep (VD 21), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Fall Down Get Up; letter of agreement; correspondence
    - Benson, Michael - Haleakala (VD 22) (IND), 1993, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      Grant application FY94 for Predictions of Fire; correspondence (1997)
    - Berg, Peter, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Correspondence; letter of agreement; artist biography
    - Berger, Mark - Alternative Media Information Center (FN 12), c. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for She's a Knockout, handwritten notes
    - Berliner, Alan NYFA - (VE 23) (IND), 1985-1994 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1991-1992, FY92, FY94) for Unfinished Business, Taking Inventory, Audiofile and Family Ties
    - Berman, Jonathan NYFA (VD 18), c.1997 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      Grant application FY97 for My Friend Paul
    - Berne, Time - Haleakala (J 221), c. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      Grant application FY90 for music composition
    - Bey, Dawoud (Ph 8), c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Brooklyn Street Portraits
    - Biddle Geoffrey (Ph 9), undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
      photographs
    - Billops, Camille - Hatch-Billops Collection (VD 19), c. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Finding Christa
    - Birch, Willie - Learning to Read Through Arts (SC 13), undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
      Grant application (undated) for Contemporary Monuments
    - Black, Stephanie - Film News Now (VD 26), undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Grant application (undated) for The Way We Look to Song
    - Blair, David (VA 21), c. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      Grant application 1988-1989 Wax
    - Bloss, Richard (VI 22), c. 1988, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Grant application (1988-1989 and undated) for video installations
    - Blumberg, Skip, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      Final 1999 Grant Report for General Operating Support
    - Blumenthal, Lyn - Artists Space, Inc. (VA 15), c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1987-1988) for True Sex and Doublecross
    - Bode, Peer, undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
      Experimental Television Center Sponsored Artist' Project list
    - Bogart, Ann - Sang-Froid, Ltd. (IND), c. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for What: Gertrude and Alice: A Likeness to Loving
    - Bogawa, Roddy - Drift Distribution (VE 28) (IND), c. 1990, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      Grant application (1990, FY94) for Some Divine Wind and Junk
    - Bohlen, A. /Ridgeway - Human Arts Association (VD 22), c. 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990) for Right Thinking and Blood in the Face
    - Bolcom - Philharmonic Symphony Society (OR 260), undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
      Sample of work submitted form
    - Boothe Power - Thought, Movement, Motor, Inc. (VE 18), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Overture; correspondence
    - Borden, Lizzie - Collective for Living Cinema (VN 22), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Working Girls
    - Greg, Bordowitz - Fund for Human Dignity, c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for AIDS public education projects
    - Bornstein, Rocky - Talking Band, Inc. (Di 4), c. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for Home Entertainment
    - Borton, Helen, c. 1992 (Box 10, Folder 79)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Brighton Beach
    - Boucherd, Linda - Harvestworks (ST 63), c. 1987, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY90) for music compositions
    - Bouiss, Elizabeth - Women Make Movies (VD 30)(IND), c. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      Grant application FY94 for Vietnam: The Women Who Served
    - Bourodimos, Angela E. - White Columns (PA 26), c. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for the end of nature and the end of history project
    - Bowes, Ed - NYFA (N 17), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      Grant application 1986-1986 for Oh No. Paula!
    - Bowes, Tom - Livewalk, Inc./Kinemetic (VN 32), c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for The Office - No Number, No Name
    - Bowie, Lester and Brass Fantasy - Brooklyn Academy of Music (JZ 137), undated (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Bowser, Pearl - Langston Hughes... (VD 207) (IND), 1991 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Midnight Ramble
    - Boyd, Kyle - There Productions (VD 35), c. 1992 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Life Matters
    - Braderman, Joan, c. 1989, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      Grant application (1989-1990, FY95) for The Incredible Shrinking Citizen and Love is the Rhythm
    - Branca, Glenn - Bang on a Can (CH 14), undated (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Brand, Bill - Parabola (FD 24), c. 1987, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990) for Home Less Home
    - Bratton, Chris - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 25), c. 1991 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Counterterror
    - Breer, Emily, c. 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      Grant application (1988-1989, 1989-1990) for Brute Charm
    - Breer, Robert - Parabola (FA 24), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Bang
    - Broughel, Barbara (MG 14), c. 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      Grant application (1984-1985, 1985-1986, 1987-1988) for The Extermination of the Soul and Tiny Moments, Tiny Thoughts
    - Brose, Lawrence - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual (VE 31), c. 1990-1998 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      Grant application (1990, FY96, FY98) for Films for Music, De Profundis and Crossing
    - Brown, Michael Henry, c. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for John Brown Project
    - Browning, Philippe - Morning Star Film Association (VN 29), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Conversations in the Underground
    - Bryant, Linda Doode - Women Make Movies (VE 39), c. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      Grant application FY96 for In the Minds of Men (MOM)
    - Buch, Rene, c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Twelfth Night production
    - Buchen, Bill and Mary - Sonic Architecture Media (CO 40), c. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Sound Engine
    - Burke, Chris -Parabola (AA 29), c. 1991 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for El Patron
    - Byard, Carole (SC 17), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      Letter of agreement; grant application FY89 for Rent Collection
    - Byrne, James - Parabola Arts Foundation (CL 38), c. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Fields
    - Cachiero - Intar, c. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Intar
    - Cage, John and Cunningham, Merce (S 31A), c. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      Grant application (undated c.1985) for Points in Space, Signals and Etudes Boreales for Arcade
    - Cale, David - Second Stage Theater, Inc. (IND), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      Grant application 1988 for Inside Brooke Waters
    - Cardillo, Rimer (MD 20), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 107)
      Grant application FY89 triptych alter sculpture
    - Carr, Laurence - Studio Arena Theater, c. 1992 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for McKinley's Follies
    - Carlomusto, Jean - Media Network (VD 53) (IND), c. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      Grant application FY95 for Rocca and her Children
    - Carrerio, Joel, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 110)
      35mm SLIDES; correspondence; project proposal for hand-made paper piece installation
    - Carrescia, Olivia - Women Make Movies (VD 43) (IND), c. 1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      Grant application (1986-1987, FY92, FY94) for Todos Santos Cuchumatan and Mayan Voices, American Lives
    - Camarda, George - NYFA (VN 37), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      Grant application FY98 for Zygote; letter of agreement 1997
    - Casabre, James, c. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 113)
      Grant application (undated) for untitled photography project; final report 1983
    - Cayler, Tom and Steven Hayes - Red Wing Performing Group, Inc. (CO 8), c. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 114)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for untitled performance collaboration; flier
    - Chalmers, Jessica - The Builders Association, c. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 115)
      Final report FY 1998-1999 for Jet Lag
    - Chadabe, Joel - Ellen Sinopoli Dance (SD 6) (IND), c. 1997 (Box 10, Folder 116)
      Correspondence; sample of work submitted forms
    - Chalfant, Henry - Bronx Council on the Arts (VD 38), undated (Box 10, Folder 117)
      Grant application (undated) for Children of the Streets - Their Lives in Progress
    - Champagne, Lenora - Segue Foundation (P 25), c. 1985, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 118)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1989-1990) for Home and Themes: Isabella Dreams the New World
    - Chang, Christine - Women Make Movies (VN 45) (IND), 1986, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      Grant application FY94 for My Heart is Burning; correspondence; letter of agreement (1986)
    - Chapman, Linda and Mary Patierno - Sang-Froid, Ltd, c. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      Grant application (FY95) for Dyke TV; final report
    - Chase, Anthony - Dagmar Collective (VE 46) (IND), c. 1993 (Box 10, Folder 121)
      Grant application FY94 for untitled film project; letter of agreement
    - Cheang, Shu Lea - Film News Now (VN 39), c. 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 122)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1989-1990) for Color Schemes and For Whom the Air Waves
    - Chaiken, Joseph - Westbeth Artist Residents Council (CO 9), c. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      Grant application FY96 for commissioned play
    - Chatham, Rhys -Harvestworks (E 123), c. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Chen, Amy (VD 43), c. 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 125)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1988-1989, 1991-1992) for Under Attack: McCarthyism and New York Chinatown and Asian Pacific Islanders
    - Chenzira, Ayoka, c. 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1987-1988) for Poets on the Dance Floor
    - Child, Abigail - NYFA (VE 39), 1991, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      Grant application (FY92, FY95) for unnamed project and By Desire; letter of agreement
    - Chin, Mel - Storefront for Art and Architecture (SC 33), undated (Box 10, Folder 128)
      Grant application (undated) for Degrees of Paradise: Installation and Preliminary Studies for the State of Heaven
    - Chinlund, Phyllis - Emmous House, Inc. (V 33D), c. 1984 (Box 10, Folder 129)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Don't Call me a Saint: The Life and Legacy of Dorthy Day
    - Chong, Ping (IND), c. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for Doppelganger
    - Chong, Ping - Fiji Theater Company, c. 1986-1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 131)
      Grant application (1986-1987, c. 1990) for Charlie Chan: A Movie and Brightness
    - Chong, Ping (and Company) - Fiji Theater Company (PW 10), c. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 132)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for The Things They Share
    - Choy, Christine and Renee Tajima (FD 257), c. 1985 and 1987 (Box 10, Folder 133)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1987-1988, 1988-1989) for unnamed film project, Shanghai Lil's and Fortune Cookie
    - Chua, Lawrence - Women's International Film (RA 64), c. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      Grant application FY95 for Critical Conditions
    - Chuma, Yoshiko - Hallwalls Inc., 1984 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Street Performance: The School of Hard Knocks Hits Buffalo!; letter of agreement
    - Dean Curtis Bear Claw, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 136)